<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>ForBo7 // Salman Naqvi</title>
<link>https://forbo7.github.io/bitsandbobs/</link>
<atom:link href="https://forbo7.github.io/bitsandbobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description>The world of ForBo7!</description>
<image>
<url>https://forbo7.github.io/images/profile.png</url>
<title>ForBo7 // Salman Naqvi</title>
<link>https://forbo7.github.io/bitsandbobs/</link>
</image>
<generator>quarto-1.6.40</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>OmniManip: Towards General Robotic Manipulation via Object-Centric Interaction Primitives as Spatial Constraints</title>
  <link>https://forbo7.github.io/bitsandbobs/posts/2025-01-21-A.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p>OmniManip is a hot new paper from Agibot and Peking University. It’s about zero shot natural language robotic manipulation tasks. A current issue with this task, and current approaches the utilize VLMs, is that VLMs lack 3D spatial understanding. They’re only trained on 2D images and video after all.</p>
<p>OmniManip utilizes an ensemble of models to achieve this goal. This is how it works at a high level.</p>
<p>A segmentation model is used to extract relevant objects from the robot’s vision. A VLM then filters out task relevant objects, and also breaks down the input task (input as text) into multiple stages.</p>
<p>Next, for each stage of the task, interaction primitives and their spatial constraints are extracted. A single view 3D generation model is used to generate meshes for all objects relevant to the task. A pose estimation model is then used to canonicalize the objects. Interaction primitives and their corresponding constraints relevant for the task are then identified by the VLM. Along the way, a LLM is used to grade various primitives and constriants.</p>
<p>Models hallucinate (in particular, the VLM). The world is not static. To overcome this, a closed loop system is introduced; a self correction mechanism based on resampling, rendering and checking. This method uses realtime feedback form the VLM, which is used to detect and then correct interaction errors. A pose tracking algorithm is also used to continuously update the poses of all relevant objects, allowing the robot to be dynamically adjusted.</p>
<p><a href="https://omnimanip.github.io/">Link to paper.</a></p>



<a onclick="window.scrollTo(0, 0); return false;" id="quarto-back-to-top"><i class="bi bi-arrow-up"></i> Back to top</a> ]]></description>
  <category>Robotics</category>
  <category>Natural Language Processing</category>
  <guid>https://forbo7.github.io/bitsandbobs/posts/2025-01-21-A.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>小和年轻</title>
  <link>https://forbo7.github.io/bitsandbobs/posts/2025-01-14-A.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p>小 can indicate whether one is young or old. For example, 她有一个小孩儿. However, you have to be careful when using 年轻, as it carries the connotation of being the opposite of old. If you’re saying you’re younger than someone, and you use 年轻, it also implies that the other person is old. 小 does not carry this connotation.</p>
<p><a href="https://resources.allsetlearning.com/chinese/vocabulary/Comparing_%22shao%22_and_%22xiao%22#To_express_.22young.22_as_an_adjective_use_.E5.B0.8F">From the Chinese Grammar Wiki (including the example sentence).</a>.</p>



<a onclick="window.scrollTo(0, 0); return false;" id="quarto-back-to-top"><i class="bi bi-arrow-up"></i> Back to top</a> ]]></description>
  <category>Mandarin</category>
  <guid>https://forbo7.github.io/bitsandbobs/posts/2025-01-14-A.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
  <title>没几个</title>
  <link>https://forbo7.github.io/bitsandbobs/posts/2025-01-02-A.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 




<p>没几个 is a way of saying a “very few” of something, rather than “not few”.</p>
<p>我认识的人很多，但没几个好朋友。</p>
<p>From the <a href="https://immersivechinese.com/">Immersive Chinese App</a>.</p>



<a onclick="window.scrollTo(0, 0); return false;" id="quarto-back-to-top"><i class="bi bi-arrow-up"></i> Back to top</a> ]]></description>
  <category>Mandarin</category>
  <guid>https://forbo7.github.io/bitsandbobs/posts/2025-01-02-A.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
